

# **UĞUR CENGİZ**

### Personal

Name

Uğur Cengiz

Address

İzmir

Phone number

+90 534 080 30 22

Email

ugurcengiz.mail@icloud.com

Date of birth

17-08-1994

Place of birth

Konak

Gender

Male

Website

ugurcengiz.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/ugurcengiz

#### Interests

- Playing Guitar
- Walking in Nature

I'm Fullstack DevOps Developer with 4 years experience. I develop web applications, microservices, API implementations using .NET Core, Laravel, Next.js. I use Vue.js, React.js for Front-end. For Database mySQL, postgreSQL. I always consider learning new things, use them and stay updated. In devolopment process i give importance using Source Control, Tests, Docker and CI/CD. Besides all this, I develop games with Unity Engine.

# Work experience

## **Software Developer**

2020 - 2023

Tagum, Izmir

I developed e-invoice creation automation system that works with JSON files which gives handy solution for clients.

I developed ERP application and create plugins that connects biggest Marketplace API's and process them to account and create auto generated-einvoices.

I developed micro-apps running background on server to check application/service health and recover in case of unexpected situations.

## Web Developer

2017 - 2018

Bulrog, Izmir

At the time i improved some Wordpress Plugins, Wrote useful tools that gets datas in csv files and create queues to send bulk-emails.

#### Web Developer

2016 - 2017

Calisto, Izmir

I developed CRM projects and improved built-in features.

## **Education and Qualifications**

### **Associate Degree**

2024

Bandirma University, Balikesir/Bandirma

## Skills

Javascript				
PHP	•			
.Net Core	•			
C#	•			
Laravel	•	•	•	
Linux/Terminal	•	•	•	
Docker	•	•	•	
Unity Game Engine	•			